Hey, I'm going to teach you exactly how
to set up Facebook ads for your web
design business. I'm not going to give
you some [__] advice like a lot of the
other people on YouTube. I'm actually
going to show you the type of ads that
are working right now when it comes to
the ad copy. So, the things that they're
actually writing on the ad that is
convincing the clients to actually click
on the ad and get a quote. And then also
the type of images that are stopping the
doom scroll right now. So instead of
them doom scrolling through Facebook
reels, they're going to get a massive
shock because they're going to see your
ad bang just pop up like that and
convince them to get a quote. So if
you're interested in learning how to set
up Facebook ads the correct way and the
best way for your web design business,
make sure you don't skip anything
because you don't want to miss anything
important. All right, so let's dive into
the video. All right, so the very first
thing we want to do is go into ads
manager and we're going to tap on
create. Right? The type of objective
that we want is leads because we want
them to fill out our instant form or the
form on our website. Right? They're not
making purchases or we don't want
traffic or awareness or engagement, any
of these other ones. They're all asks.
They suck really bad. So, we're going to
skip past all them and we're going with
leads. Name the campaign, whatever you
want to do it. But let's break down the
campaign into three right now. So, the
campaign level is based around ad
budget. All right. The adset level is
purely around conversion targeting. So
if you want the conversion location to
be on your website or an instant form,
picking the correct page to run the ads
on and then also the location targeting
as well. All right. So and then we have
the ad level which is you know as you
could imagine it's the actual ad. So the
magic, right? It's the thing that people
see that stops them from dream scrolling
that they click on and get a quote from
you. You also design the actual instant
form there as well. The adset level is
where you pick what type of conversion
location you want. But down here, if you
did pick Instant Forms, this is where
you design it to make it more qualifying
so you don't get any [__] leads. And
I'll teach you exactly how to do that.
So, we're going to start off in the
campaign level. I recommend just a daily
budget to start off with. If you're from
Australia, $50 to $100 per day. If
you're from the United States, $35 to
$70 per day. And if you're from the UK,
$25 to $50 per day as well. All right.
So, we're going to just tap on next now
because there's nothing else we need to
do in the campaign level. So, to start
off, we're starting with the
conversions. The conversion location
that we want is going to be Instant
Forms, right? I personally recommend it
because they don't tap on your ad and
get taken to some shitty poor loading
website, which hopefully I mean, if
you're a web design person, your website
should be pretty damn fantastic and load
pretty fast. But, you know, there is
always that risk. All right? And with
Instant Forms, it keeps them directly on
Facebook. Super easy to set up, too. And
at the end of the day, you most likely
just want them to fill out a form. So,
this is the best way to do it. Right?
Then, you just want to select your
Facebook page down here. Here I'm just
using my demonstration ad page which is
what I use for all these tutorials which
is just my Daniel Dimsey page for
performance goal. Here's a really good
tip for you. I recommend having this on
maximize number of leads. Uh I don't
bother with maximize number of
conversion leads because you end up just
paying a premium price to appear to a
little bit higher intent audiences. But
the thing is you can just make the other
audience super high intent regardless by
just having a qualifying form, which is
what I'm going to show you anyway. So,
if you want the same results in leads,
but for a cheaper result, just keep this
on maximize number of leads. Um, and
then we're going to scroll down past
here and we're going to go straight to
audience. Now, I'm going to teach you
exactly how you should be doing your
audience targeting. All right, if you're
going to target certain, you know,
states or anything like that, you can do
that in here very easily. Like this
shit's pretty simple, guys. But since
you can basically work from wherever,
um, I just recommend targeting your
whole country itself, as long as you all
speak the same language, and just doing
it like this. Like if I was going to run
this web design ad, I would just target
all of Australia, right? This is just
pretty damn easy. Unless I wanted to
make very specific campaigns for
different areas. I'd have like one for
the major cities. So, you know, web
design in Melbourne, web design in
Brisbane. But for this particular ad
that I'm going to show you, I'm going
after a certain category of
contractor/trade, whichever you want to
call it. In Australia, we call them
tradies. Uh in America, I'm sure you
call them contractors, but you know,
you'll understand what I'm talking about
when we get to the actual ad level. So,
for this, I'm just going to target the
actual whole of Australia. All right.
Now, we're going to scroll down, and
we're just going to tap on next. Real
quick, if you're enjoying the value in
this video, I have my full advertising
course linked straight down the
description. I go through everything I
know about Google Ads, Facebook ads, and
automating your entire business. It's an
absolute no-brainer to get. I go through
all of my templates, in-depth market
research and optimizations that I have
when it comes to Google Ads and Facebook
ads to optimize the account to perform
better and better the longer you run
ads, right? I teach you all the free
stuff like how to actually set up the
Google Ads and Facebook Ads account on
YouTube. But if you want to know how to
really actually optimize the absolute
hell out of those campaigns to get as
much profit as possible, that's straight
in the course. That's all the secrets
that I can't achieve for free on
YouTube. If you're interested, go jump
into it.
>> Now, here's exactly where the magic
happens. Let's scroll down now. So,
we're going to go down to add creative.
By the way, you want to keep this on
single image or video ad. This is just
the best one in my opinion. Tap on setup
creative. And we're going to tap on
image ad. All right. So, I've selected
my image here. We're just going to tap
on next. And we just want to make all
these on original. Now, as you can
probably tell right now, this image is
focused on electricians or electrical
businesses and their website design and
SEO. Right. As you can see, here's the
image itself. This is actually a really
high converting uh type of image that
you can use for web design when it comes
to Facebook ads. We've used this a
ridiculous amount for one of the web
designers that we've been running ads
for. And this obviously is just a like a
replication of that style. I have full
templates in my advertising course, by
the way. That's linked straight down the
description if you wanted this exact
template. So, you can just copy and
paste this [__] and get it live in your
business ASAP. But yeah, we've got the
um pointing out the exact, you know,
people that we're looking for. also
electricians, you know, keyword website
design, which is obviously what we're
doing, and SEO as well. And then bang,
here's a little photo of for the actual
website that we've designed for an
electrical business as well, right? It's
pretty damn simple and pretty damn good.
Like, this is really easy when it comes
to actually creating images. Like, you
can just make bulk different images when
it comes to Facebook ads. Test them all
out and you'll find a couple winners
pretty quickly. So, we're going to go
past here now. Tap on next. And we're
going to put in all of this stuff a
little bit later. I don't want to put it
in right here just because it looks like
[__] when you put it in right here cuz
you can't actually see it on the ad.
We're going to tap on next. We're going
to get our images generated here by the
holy AI, our new god, and we're going to
see what it comes up with. So, right
now,
okay, this is [__] This is [__]
Ah, slight potential, but it's [__]
[__] [__] [__] [__]
Um,
[__] [__] [__] I mean, that one kind
of looks a little bit cool, but still
[__] Well, AI sucks right now. It's
verified. Um, no, no, they have actually
came up with a few goodies beforehand
and a couple of other ads that I've
created, but these ones currently, these
are dog [__] Let's skip past these. And
I remove all of these. They're all dog
[__] I'm glad Facebook finally knows
that I'm sick of flicking all of these
off. They suck. All right. Can't be
bothered explaining it into crazy degree
why they suck, but basically, you want
full control when it comes to Facebook
ads. at least a large amount of control.
So, you don't want things like text
improvement, enhanced CTA, and all that
type of [__] getting in here because
it's just going to change the words that
you put on the ad, which is what you
don't want to happen. So, I like to keep
on add overlays, visual touch-ups, add
music, and flex media. It's not too bad.
I'm going to [__] it off right now.
These are the main ones that are the
best in my opinion. We're going to tap
on done. We're going to scroll down
because right now we've got the bare
bones of the ad. By the way, this is how
you can see it. So, Facebook feed,
Instagram feed, and there's all these
different, you know, other versions that
you can see as well. We're going to go
into the primary text and paste in our
large persuasive ad copy. Bang. Here's
my ad copy here. You do the work
properly. You show up. You deliver
quality. Yet, online, the cowboys are
winning the clicks because their
websites look more professional than
yours, right? Really stick the knife in,
twist it around, really get them
hurting. All right? Because we want them
to read this [__] and be like, "Wow, I
do need a better website because I'm
losing out on money right now." Okay.
Now, with this ad copy, I'm just going
to scroll through it. I'm not going to
read you the whole [__] thing, all
right? Because it just be boring. If you
want to, you can pause it, read it,
whatever. Um, but obviously, feel free.
I I give you full permission to steal
this [__] if you want. Like, if you want
to steal the ad copy in here and just
change it around for your business,
[__] go for it. I really don't care.
I want you to get the best results
possible because then you'll realize
that I actually give out true value on
this YouTube page and in my course and
it will actually get you to dive in,
join the course and really scale your
web design business with the secret
strategies that I have in there and then
you can thank me about it later on. All
right. So, or you can thank me now by
smashing like on this video. That's
super helpful as well. So, for the
actual headline, we're going to do this
painoint focus as well, which uh I'm
going to paste in something right now.
So, bang, just like that. Your website
is costing you jobs, right? But it rolls
in with the same pain points we're
starting off with, you know, about them
being really good at their job yet, the
[__] guys are getting all the leads
because obviously, you know, their
website just looks better. All right,
because this is literally costing them
money by not getting this fixed. All
right, so this is a really, really,
really good uh CTA. All right, and what
I will do quickly is I'm just going to
actually change this to um I've just
changed this over to tap the get quote
button to get your quote. All right.
Now, I changed this over just because
it's a little bit easier than apply cuz
apply just doesn't work as well in my
opinion. So, we're going to make this
get quote. So, we're going to change
this call to action button here to get
quote. And for the description, we're
just going to put in some sort of social
proof like like 79 electrical websites
built. Now, the reason why this isn't
popping up on the ad like right here is
just because this is a little bit too
long. But depending on, you know, what
platform you see this ad on, whether you
see it on mobile, the tiny small iPhone
or the iPhone Max, the iPhone Max,
you'll be able to actually see the um
description cuz obviously it's wider. If
you see this on a MacBook, tablet, iPad,
whatever, you'll obviously see the
description, but this is clearly just
the um smallest one right now. So, let
me just show you what that looks like.
Bang. As you can see, it popped up down
here. Sorry, it is, you know, quite um
quite small uh because obviously I've
stretched it out cuz of the ad copy. But
yeah, this is what it would look like,
right? Obviously, I'm going to change
this back to your website is costing
you.
All right, so our website is built now
and it looks absolutely killer. What we
should do now is just go and create the
instant form. I'm going to give you a
explanation how to do this. Just tap on
create form. So you got to go to
destination first. Tap on create form. I
put this on more volume. I keep the
sharing settings as open and I just have
flexible delivery on. That's fine. Tap
on next and we're going to remove the
greeting because this is just a [__]
waste of time. If anyone ever tells you
putting a greeting, just don't listen to
them. Like it doesn't do anything good
for your business besides make people
bounce off cuz they don't understand
what the [__] is going on. All right?
And it does happen cuz old ladies get on
there and they're like, I don't know
what this is. Obviously, this this ad
isn't going to go to old ladies, but you
might get very old electricians or like
60 years old want to update their, you
know, page that's been built in [__]
2001. Right now, what we're going to do
here first is we're going to add in
questions. We're just going to have
multiple choice or short answer. I like
to have three to four qualifying
questions. Okay, this is purely because
we just want to [__] qualify them and
make sure they're actually suited to get
a quote from us. And we don't want to
get tire kickass [__] leads in here who
just, you know, enter in their details
and don't actually answer the phone,
right? So, what we want to do is have
this on multiple choice and have yeah
like about three of these multiple
choice questions and a short answer
question. What I like to do for the
questions is, you know, you can ask
around budget, best form of contact,
stuff like that. And I also like to get
the um short answer area and I just make
them enter in their phone number
manually because sometimes when they get
to this side of the page because
sometimes when they get to this part of
the form, it'll put in their phone
number, right? but it will give one of
their old Facebook phone numbers that
they started Facebook with and it's not
up to date and you won't get their
number and you think it's a Dudley but
really they just didn't realize that it
entered in their old number. All right,
so how you write in the questions just
type it in here whatever it is minimum
character maximum character and then
obviously they just type out their
answer here. So so here's a question
here. What's your phone number? Then
they just type it in. So you know
maximum five characters to you know 15.
All right. So this way you guarantee get
an actual phone number and they don't go
jam a bunch of random [__] in here.
Well, they might, but you know, very
rare. Um, at least you know straight off
the bat that they're a dud lead if
that's the case. Not that you're going
to get many, but like, you know, but
yeah, um, with multiple choice, just
type in your question. Then you can have
in multiple different answers. The
answers will just appear here. They can
just tap on whatever they want. All
right. So, you could have budget and
then have examples of prices and
everything like that. But once you've
done that, scroll down. Make sure this
isn't optional. We want their [__]
phone number. I know we're getting it
twice, but we need to be sure. Now, we
just want to put in here anything else
we might find is relevant. So, we might
get their work email as well if we want.
Really up to you. Um, if they don't have
a good website right now, they might be
new, so they might not actually have a
work email. So, I wouldn't really bother
with that one right now. Just grab their
email, full name, and phone number. Tap
on next. Put in your privacy right here.
You can actually remove this if you
want. Um, it's completely up to you, but
it does make you look a little bit more
professional if you put in a policy. You
can honestly just link this directly to
your website if you want. But once
you've done that, tap on next. Then you
can put in thanks, you're all set. And
you can actually have the description as
like you'll receive a quote from us
within the next 24 to 48 hours or just
anything like that or a phone call,
whatever it is. And you can actually
make this on call business if you prefer
them to call you right after they've
filled out the form. Or you can have
this on go to website and link this to a
place where it has like all of your
proof of your electrical ads or whatever
[__] ad you're doing. If you're doing
it for hotels or whatever, I I don't
[__] know what you're doing it for.
So, it's like if you have proof of that,
you could send them to a page
specifically about that proof so they
go, "Okay, this [__] looks good. This
guy knows what he's doing." All right.
So, you could have like view our
electrical website, something like that.
And tap on create form and then you just
go down, tap on publish, and then you're
done. If you're the type of business
owner that doesn't want to waste any
time or energy on trial and error, and
you just want to know everything when it
comes to Google Ads and Facebook ads and
exactly how to make unbelievably
profitable campaigns for your business,
there's a link in the description to my
advertising course. I go through
everything I know when it comes to
in-depth market research, the
optimizations that I can't share for
free on YouTube that actually continue
the growth of your campaigns so you can
really scale your business, and also all
of my marketing templates that I
literally use for my marketing agency
when I run all these ads for local
businesses. If you're interested in
that, go to the link and buy the course.
Hey. Hey. Hey.